One evening coming in with a candle I was startled
to hear him say a little tremulously, "I am lying
here in the dark waiting for death."  The light was
within a foot of his eyes.  I forced myself to
murmur, "Oh nonsense!" and stood over him as if
transfixed.

Anything approaching the change that came over his
features I have never seen before, and hope never
to see again.  Oh, I wasn't touched.  I was
fascinated.  It was as though a veil had been rent.
I saw on that ivory face the expression of sombre
pride, of ruthless power, of craven terror - of an
intense and hopeless despair.  Did he live his life
again in every detail of desire, temptation, and
surrender during that supreme moment of complete
knowledge?  He cried in a whisper at some image,
at some vision, - he cried out twice, a cry that
was no more than a breath - 

"The horror!  The horror!"
