﻿Observations on the creatures, Part 1, Issue 5...

...exceptionally tough hides and, perhaps even more 
importantly, the simplistic anatomy, makes them
impervious to all but the most determined assault
with conventional weapons.  Like insects, their
strategy is to reproduce fast and avoid the heavy
dependence on complex organs such as brains that
makes most larger animals so vulnerable...

...Dr Bob Karlson's preliminary research into tumour 
growth on the new samples turned up more surprising
results.  Despite being around 150 percent more 
susceptible to cancers than the control group, the
new samples were also found to be better able to
tolerate them and indeed adapt to them.  The
committee notes that, if they could be controlled,
the creatures could make a perfect weapon of last 
resort in the event (God forbid) of a nuclear war, 
since instead of killing them the radiation would 
in all likelihood make them stronger...

...conclusion, the unique physiology of the
creatures, if it can really be harnessed, represents 
a powerful weapon for the free world in the fight
against Communism.  Just think of all the good we 
could do with this kind of power in our hands!
