25th August, 1968
This document is classified

To: Colonel Bob Kurtz, Special Operations
From: United States Army High Command

Having reviewed the latest set of data your team
has sent us we have decided on the following policy, 
that:

1. The field experiments MUST be halted as a 
matter of utmost urgency.  

2. It is in the interests the United States public 
and indeed of mankind as a whole that, in order to
prevent it from falling into the wrong hands, the 
craft be transferred to a location in the United 
States and its existence remain an official secret 
for the forseeable future.

3. While we are preparing the equipment to dig it
out and ship it, the craft must continue to be guarded
scrupulously in order to prevent its discovery by
hostile interests.
