15th December, 1968

Note to all units: Unfortunately as we are not a front
line base we do not have much heavy armour 
available to us.  In order to be able to respond
better to the creatures attacks, we have volunteered
Private Bob Neuman to maintain several weapons 
caches which can be quickly accessed
by defenders.  So far we have:

- A captured RPG7 in the food storage area above the 
kitchens and the canteen.

- An M60 in the armory by the airfield.

- An M79 and a vest full of ammo in the rec room 
beneath the C/O quarters.
