Observations on the creatures, Part 4, Issue 7...

...control system was established.  Although
still very imperfect at this stage, we do seem
to be able to give them creatures orders which
they will obey to the extent that their 
intelligence permits...

...Unfortunately the most persistant problem,
which we have not yet been able to make any
headway at all with, is training them not
to attack us.  The only thing we know of which
they will not attack is members of their own
species (and there are even some exceptions to
this)...

...therefore proposed that if a human being 
were injected with the drug instead, it would 
appear to the creatures as a member of their 
own species and therefore not be attacked, and
that this could be adopted as a temporary
solution.  However, it is unclear to what 
extent the same side effects would...

...speculated that the creatures subscribe to a
hierarchical leadership structure, like ordinary
animal groups, where if a member of the
pack challenges and kills the dominant male,
he will become the new leader of the pack...
