Memo: 20th September 1968
Lt-Col. Bob Samuels, C/O, Buon Rau Bang Nui.

Recieved a message from Command today concerning the
recent visit of Colonel Bob Kurtz to Buon Rau Bang Nui.
They wanted to know, was he acting strangely at all?
Apparently they'd had some peculiar messages from him:
a couple of human ears sent in paper envelopes.

I told them I don't care whatever's going on up there,
I got bigger things to worry about.  It's been two days
since we lost contact with the upriver patrol, and even
if their radio broke down they should have returned by
now.  Yet all our intelligence shows no enemy activity 
in that sector.  Where the Hell are those guys?
