I remember when I was with special forces.  It
seems a thousand centuries ago.  We went into
a camp to innoculate some children.  We left the
camp after we had innoculated the children from
polio.  And this old man came running after us
and he was crying, he couldn't see.  We went back
there, and THEY had come and hacked off every 
innoculated arm.  There they were in a pile.  A
pile of little arms.  And, I remember 
I cried, I wept like some grandmother, I wanted to
tear my teeth out, I didn't know what I wanted to
do.  And I want to remember it, I never want to
forget.  

And then I realised, like I was shot with a diamond 
- a diamond bullet right through my forehead, and 
I thought my god the genius of that.  The genius, 
the WILL to do that.  Perfect, genuine, complete, 
crystalline, pure.  And then I realised, THEY were 
stronger than we.  Because they could stand that 
these were not monsters, these were men - trained 
cadres - these men, who fought with their hearts, 
who had families, who had children, who were filled 
with love, but they had the strength to do that.  
If I had ten divisions of those men then our 
troubles here would be over very quickly.

You have to have men who are moral, and at the 
same time who are able to utilise their primordal 
instincts to kill, without feeling, without passion, 
without JUDGEMENT, because it's judgement that 
defeats us.
