Journal of Colonel Bob Fish
28th May 1968

Kurtz's visit ended today.  He set off at dawn, heading
further inwards into the jungle and the Cambodian border.

Before he left he told me a story that took place during
one of his earlier tours.  He and his men were under
heavy NVA fire near a village in Dinh Lo province.
They were surrounded, but had been ordered to defend
the village.  It was clear, however, that the enemy
was being supplied with ammunition by some of the
villagers.  What's more, knowing that American troops 
would be loth to shoot at children, the enemy was
using the local children to ferry ammo between them.

After almost twelve hours of intense fighting Kurtz
had lost nearly half of his men.  Frustrated, he
ordered the remaining ones to start firing at the kids.
Running openly back and forth, they made easy targets.
With their supply lines cut, the NVA was finally forced
to retreat and Kurtz held the village.
