Dearest Angela,

I know it has been a long time since I last wrote,
and I apologise for that.  Ever since Colonel Kurtz
left our base, there have been some peculiar things
happening around here.  The situation is getting
quite out of control.  The local people say Kurtz
has made a pact with the devil.  I cannot be any
more specific than this, since I think this letter
would not make it past the censors if I was.  But I
fear for my life.  Give my love to Mom and Pop, and 
tell them I've moved on from that whole Oedipus 
thing, and I urge them to as well.

Related to that; I have some bad news for you.  I'm
afraid I can no longer continue our engagement.  I
feel it is best that you know: I've found someone else.
His - yes, his - name is Bob, just like mine.  What a
coincidence, eh?  He sleeps in the bunk opposite me,
and was always one of my best buddies here, but
recently we decided to take it one step further and 
declared our undying love for one another.  Do not
judge me too harshly, Angela; the love of a man for
for another man is a noble and beautiful thing, and
impossible to resist when it takes you in its hand.

Yours faithfully,
Bob
