Journal of Dr. Bob Lewis
10th December, 1968

The captive creatures in the laboratory continue to exhibit
the same astonishing degree of agression as they have been
doing since they were caught.  They mercilessly attack and
devour any live animals we feed them, but remain strangely
disinterested in meat that has been dead for longer than
a few hours.  This is surely not a strategy that could have
arisen naturally, through evolution.

Besides being unnaturally vicious they are also deceptively
strong.  Bob nearly had his hand torn off by one of them
earlier today, and we are all becoming worried that their 
cages may not be strong enough.  Two more patrols failed
to return today, and the mood among the men is sharply
deteriorating.

-----

In light of all this I have hidden The Gem in the vault and
sealed the door with a combination lock.  To unlock the 
door one must break the fuses in the following pattern:
1:B, 2:D, 3:A, 4:D, 5:E.  Breaking the fuses requires
considerable force to be applied; a shot from my .45
ought to do it.  Failiure to break them in the right
sequence will result in a nuclear explosion and the deaths
of thousands of innocent people.  I believe this will be
an adequate deterrent to anyone wishing to take away my Gem.

I hope no one accidentally knocks them or anything.  I keep
telling the guys not play with my stuff but they never
listen do they?  But the important thing is that The Gem is
safely hidden.  The only way to find out the combination
would be to read this journal, and I don't plan to leave this
just lying around!  Sally says my performance isn't as good
without the mystical powers of The Gem but frankly I pay her
good money so I don't know what she's got to complain about.
