19th December 1968
0500 Hrs

The creatures have overrun the perimeter and those of us 
who survived have fallen back into the main buildings and
barricaded ourselves inside.  We've put all our remaining
supplies and ammo in a big pile on the ground floor of
this building, and now we are just waiting.

All night long we've been hearing the sound of gunfire, 
shouts and screams from the nearby buildings.  I've been 
awake for nearly 30 hours now but I couldn't sleep.  None 
of us could.  I'm so tired.  Our food and ammunition are 
running out.  The chain of command is breaking down, 
people are openly disobeying orders from their superiors.  
Lt. Bob Heller disappeared a few hours ago: the story was
he was taking a piss outside and the creatures got him, but
I think it was a couple of the men.  Bob was always 
unpopular with the men.
