20th December, 1968

To whom it may concern:

It's no use, we've been overrun.  We should have
exterminated the creatures when we had the chance, 
but there are too many of them now.  They're not smart,
but they just keep coming.  I can't take it anymore.
My entire unit is gone.  I don't want to become one of
them.
I've been saving a few cartridges in my old 870 specially
ever since we began running low on ammo.  If you're 
already dead, they lose interest in you.  I don't want 
my body walking around killing people after I'm dead.
If you should read this, don't try and contact my
family.  It's best if they don't know how or why it
happened.  Just get out of here.  Get away from this
place.  Run, I tell you, run!  Oh shit, I hear them.
They're coming.  This is it!
Sincerely,
Bob Dickinson.

PS. Look out, there's a zombie behind you!  Kidding.
