Journal of Colonel Bob Fish
23rd November 1968

Another man was killed by the creatures today.  The
grunts are becoming frightened and unruly, morale is
dropping fast.  On the plus side, Viet Cong presence
in the area is also decreasing, and the ones we do
run into always seem to be on their way out of here.
The creatures obviously have them spooked as well.

A patrol by Lang Dau caught some prisoners and we 
asked them if they knew where the creatures were
coming from.  According to the report they just
babbled incoherent gook-speak, but there was one
word that kept being repeated: Kurtz.  I am now
certain the creatures come from Kurtz.  The man is
a visionary, he's a prodigy, an ambassador of mercy,
and science, and progress, and fuck knows what
else.  We need, for the guidance of the cause
entrusted to us by the United States and the free
world, so to speak, higher intelligence, wide
sympathies, and a singleness of purpose.  And so
He comes here, a special being, with the power to
do all this.  He has some great purpose with the
creatures, you may be sure of it.
