Journal of Dr. Bob Lewis
4th December, 1968

Today some of the men were able to capture a live specimen
of one of the creatures for the first time.  Their numbers
have shown a dramatic increase over the past few weeks -
patrols are reporting contact with one or more of them as
often as three or four times a day now, which suggests
that they must be breeding at a truly phenomenal rate.
So little is known about them!

Our analysis of their anatomy has so far proved fruitless;
we remain just as baffled about their physiology, their 
physical needs, and of course their origin, as we ever 
were.  This  captured specimen represents a marvellous and 
unique opportunity to observe their behaviour in the 
controlled atmosphere of the laboratory.  If only we had 
better facilities here.  A military hospital is hardly an 
ideal place to conduct scientific research.

-----

All my requests to Command for better equipment have so
far gone completely unanswered.  This does not surprise me.
Indeed, it merely serves to further confirm my suspicions
that these creatures are not a hitherto undiscovered 
indigenous species or an aberration of nature, but are in 
fact entirely the product of the American government.  We 
have been hearing rumours about a revolutionary secret 
project to be tested on the field in 'nam since early '66.  

It seems to me that the experiment has gone badly wrong.  
The creatures are devastating the local wildlife and 
threatening the people.  There is sure to be an outcry back 
home, when the press finds out.
