(Translated from Vietnamese)

To whoever should find this,

I am writing this in the hope that someday this madness
will end and someone will read my words and know what
took place in this town.  I feel sure that I will be
dead by then.

The first attacks by the creatures came several months
ago.  Men started returning from the jungle talking of 
attacks by strange, violent animals... or sometimes they
just didn't return at all.  They believed they were evil
spirits.  At first few people believed them, but we soon 
found out first-hand exactly what they were talking about.

I remember the first time a Creature was sighted in the
town.  It killed two people and badly lacerated a third
before someone managed to find one of the local GIs, who
shot it with his machine gun.  We started to lock our
doors and make sure our children stayed inside, but we
were disorganised and we simply weren't prepared for how
many of them there were.  

-----

By the time we realised the extent of the problem, it
was too late.  A lot of people tried to flee the town, 
but I doubt if they got far - the jungle was swarming
with creatures by that time.  The rest of us started
to band together, barricading ourselves inside the
largest buildings and preparing for the worst.

That was how General Dhong rose to power.  He claimed
to be high up in the North Vietnamese Army, but who 
knows if that's true or not?  All that mattered was 
that people followed him.  He gave speeches in the 
centre of town, and everyone would come and cheer.
Instead of attributing the creatures to evil spirits, 
as everyone else had been doing, he placed the blame 
for them squarely on the Americans.  That was why the 
local Viet Cong supported him.  

The General got everyone to erect huge barricades in
the streets to keep the creatures out.  (Later, we
realised they were also to keep the people in.)  At
first it was voluntary, but soon his VC army began
threatening and beating anyone who did not co-operate,
or was considered not to be working hard enough.  
People supported him, those that weren't being beaten,
because he was keeping the creatures out.

-----

All food and fuel in the town was confiscated by
the General's men.  Ostensibly this was so that it
could be rationed out fairly in the event of a
protracted siege, but it also meant we were now
dependant on the General for everything.  Some people
objected to having their houses raided and their 
supplies taken, but they were accused of having
'bourgeous ideals' and sympathising with the Americans,
who were the ones responsible for this mess.

The General began having public trials in the centre
of town, where supposed dissenters to what he called
The Revolution were publicly indicted, tried and 
convicted.  They were always guilty.  They were then
strung up outside the barricades for the creatures 
to devour.  

Later, he came up with the idea of capturing creatures
and feeding 'enemies of The Revolution' to them in
the stadium - which he renamed 'The People's Stadium'.
It wasn't a misnomer.  The People loved it, standing
up and cheering ecstatically at the site of those who
had once been their friends and family being torn to
shreds by creatures.  I believe as long as the General
is able to supply them with food and executions, and
keep the creatures out, he will have their full support.

-----

I have managed to escape from the General's compound, 
and am hiding out in this apartment block.  If the 
General's men find me, I'm dead.  If the creatures 
find me, I'm dead.  I've placed tripmines on the 
entrances to the building, and the area is booby-
trapped.  It's a poor defense but it's better than
nothing.  

I have found an old minibus near the General's
compound that still has some fuel in it.  I believe
it could come in useful somehow.  In order to prevent
anyone else from using it, I've removed the tyres
and hidden them in various places around the town.
I altered the axle to make sure only those tires
would fit it, and marked them with the symbols from
a pack of playing cards: Hearts, Diamonds, Clubs
and Spades.

One is hidden on the top floor of this apartment,
another is in a stall in the market place, another 
is next to the barricade where the prisoners are 
hanged, and the last is in the old gas station.

The gas station is barricaded shut, but I think the
creatures got in through the sewers; there's no sign
of life there anyway.  You can get anywhere through 
the sewers; I even heard a couple of 'enemies of the 
people' once escaped from the prison cells through 
the sewers.
