﻿Captain Freeman,

I thought you were dead, but rumour has it you are
still alive.  If this is true, there are some things
you should know about your mission - and about Kurtz.  

Colonel Kurtz passed through this base back in June
on his way upriver.  He was on a mission to field test 
some secret new weapon.  He had a group of SOG guys 
with him, I didn't ask.  Later on, late August, I 
heard that the field tests were cancelled.

It was around September that we started getting messages
from Command asking about Kurtz's stay here: had he
been acting strangely at all, had he said anything
unusual?  It was also around then that the first 
creatures were sighted.

On the fourth of November another man from Special 
Forces stopped with us on his way upriver.  His 
mission was identical to yours: to assassinate
Colonel Kurtz.  No more was heard from him until
late yesterday evening, when we recieved a letter from 
him carried by a nervous Vietnamese courier.  The guy 
had been running across creature-infested countryside 
all night, I don't know how he made it through - 
anyway he was pretty desperate to get out of here.

-----

The letter read simply:

"When there's no more room in Hell, the dead will
walk the Earth."

This morning I had my last radio conversation with
Command.  They told me they were assuming their
assassin was dead and they had sent another man -
you - to kill the Colonel.  Then I told them
about the letter.  I also asked for more backup 
to fight the creatures, as I have done every day 
this week.

There was a long pause and a whispered conversation
which I did not catch properly.  Then the guy on
the radio told me in a hurried voice that backup 
would be sent very soon now - and hung up.  We have
been unable to establish contact with them since 
then.

It is clear to me now that the generals want us all 
dead, and soon they will come to destroy us.  I have 
decided to take my chances upriver.  I will wait for
you for a few hours in the boathouse, but if you do
not come I will go on alone.

Lt-Col. Bob Samuels, C/O, Buon Rau Bang Nui.
